IVANA KATIĆ



 \checkmark

katic.ivana@ymail.com



A. Mihanovica, 42a Zapresic, Croatia



Portfolio Web Page

https://github.com/kativana/ivana-katic.github.io

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ivana-katic/

Github

https://github.com/kativana

Heroku

https://curious-socialapp.herokuapp.com/accounts/login/

Medium

https://medium.com/@katic.ivana

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

PYTHON

Beautiful Soup, Pandas, NLTK, Textblob, Gensim, spaCy, Scrapy, Matplotlib, Tkinter, Pygame, Django

SQLite, HTML, CSS, Jekyll

PROGRAMMING PROJECTS

I've worked on a variety of projects, from creating social media applications to scraping and analyzing U.S. presidential speeches using natural language processing. For more details, please visit my webpage.

https://github.com/kativana/ivana-katic.github.io

U.S. Presidents` Rhetoric on China Reddit Analysis PyPlant Curious Ninja

WORKING LANGUAGES

English, Chinese, German, Croatian

EDUCATION

FUDAN UNIVERSITY,

SHANGHAI

PhD in International Relations

9/2014 - 6/2018

TONGJI UNIVERSITY,

SHANGHAI

Chinese language

9/2018 - 7/2019

EXPERIENCE

INDEPENDENT CONSULTANT

2020 -

Translating Lao Tzu - Tao Te Ching from the Chinese language to

Exploring Chinese laws

Analyzing Chinese markets

Translating documents to and from the Chinese language

Searching for and contacting Chinese partner companies

FACULTY OF POLITICAL SCIENCE. ZAGREB

Master in Journalism and Political Communication 9/2009 - 6/2011

FACULTY OF POLITICAL SCIENCE, ZAGREB

Bachelor in Journalism and PR 9/2005 - 9/2009

CERTIFICATES

ALGEBRA UNIVERSITY COLLEGE, ZAGREB

Python developer 11/2022 - 6/2023

HSK 5, SHANGHAI Chinese Proficiency Test 2019

FUDAN UNIVERSITY, SHANGHAI

General Advanced Scholar

9/2021 - 2/2022

EU COMMISSION, BRUSSELS BB TRAINEE, COMMUNICATIONS

02/2020 - 08/2020

Creating an analytical framework for digital data analysis, writing a handbook

Creating reports and evaluations

Managing and monitoring social media

Creating web content related to the topics of sustainable development and the circular economy

FUDAN UNIVERSITY, SHANGHAI

PHD CANDIDATE

2014-2018

Teaching, assisting and presenting lectures in International Relations

Theories

Organizing workshops

Organizing international conferences

Conducting and writing researches and analyses

Giving speeches in Chinese

RADIO 101, ZAGREB NEWS EDITOR, JOURNALIST

2010 - 2014

Reporting and presenting news

Conducting interviews

Choosing topics and assigning tasks

Making schedules

JABUKA TV, ZAGREB NEWS EDITOR. JOURNALIST

2009 - 2010

Reporting and presenting news

Conducting interviews

Choosing topics and assigning tasks

Making schedules